Gordon Shrum collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Gordon Shrum collection
1922 - 1989
F-31
Q106644089
38 cm of textual records 27 sound recordings 6 moving image documents
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION Collection includes sound recordings and moving images in original formats as well as access copies for some but not all items; includes 44 audio cassettes, 18 audio reels, 13 3/4" videocassettes (Umatic tapes), 2 VHS videocassettes, and 1 optical disk (DVD).
Archives and Records Management Department
The University Archives acquires, preserves and makes available three categories of materials: (1) the official records of the University, including those created by the Board of Governors, Senate, University committees, faculties, departments and administrative offices; (2) materials documenting the wider University community; and (3) historical research collections that promote the teaching and research activities of the University.
The Archives was established within the University Library in 1968 when librarian Liisa Fagerlund was appointed University Archivist on a half-time basis. She continued in this post until 1975 when she left the University. From 1975 to 1978, the Archives functioned within the Special Collections division of the Library. Archival duties were carried out by various library staff members. In 1978, the University Archives was established as a separate administrative unit outside of the Library. Donald Baird, recently retired as University Librarian, became University Archivist and held this position until his retirement in 1990. Jim Ross served as University Archivist from 1991 to 1993, and was succeeded by Ian Forsyth in 1994.
When the Archives was a function of the University Library, the University Archivist reported to the University Librarian. When the Archives was established as a separate administrative unit, the University Archivist reported directly to the University President. The reporting structure changed in 1986 when the University Archivist reported to the Vice-President, Research/Information Systems; in 1990, when the University Archivist reported to the Associate Vice-President, Academic; and in 1996, when the University Archivist reported to the Registrar/Dean of Students.
published
Full
Revised
Title based on the contents of the collection.
Collection is comprised primarily of interview material in the form of audio and video tapes, transcripts and notes. The material provides both a broad biographical overview of the life and achievements of Gordon Shrum and a description of his work at SFU in particular. The collection includes a copy of Shrum's doctoral thesis and a scrapbook that was given to Gordon Shrum in 1983.
Collection includes textual records, photographs, audio cassettes, audio reels, U-matic video tapes, and VHS video tapes.
The collection was arranged by the Archivist.
Archives and Records Management Department; Shrum, Gordon; Office of the Chancellor; Sound recordings; Moving images; Photographic materials; Textual records
No further accruals are expected.
The collection was compiled by the staff of the University Archives over a period of years.
Please consult the inventory for the Gordon M. Shrum Papers, F-32, and the inventory for the Office of the Chancellor, F-3.
There are no access restrictions relating to privacy, but access to the original moving images and sound recordings is restricted due to the fragility of the physical storage media. Consult the reference archivist for more information relating to access.
File and item lists are available.
- Doctoral thesis, 1922 - 1923; F-31-1; 3 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of a bound volume entitled Researches in Physics. The volume contains Gordon Shrum's doctoral thesis, "The Doublet Separation of the Balmer Lines," and two reprints about Shrum's research with his doctoral supervisor, J. C. McLennan, on the liquefaction of hydrogen and helium.
  - Researches in Physics, 1922 - 1923; F-31-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 31-1)
    Textual records
    Open
- Biographical materials interviews, 1972 - 1986; F-31-2; 28 cm of textual records 24 sound recordings 1 moving image document; Physical description: series includes 39 audio cassettes, 10 audio reels, 7 3/4" videocassettes (Umatic tape), and 1 VHS videocassette. This includes both originals and access copies; access copies have not been made for all items.
  Series consists of records that provide a broad biographical view of the entire life of Gordon Merritt Shrum.
  Arrangement of the series into sub-series was provided by the archivist based on the contents of the materials.
  Access to the original moving images and sound recordings is restricted due to the fragility of the physical storage media. Consult the reference archivist for information about access.
  - Autobiography with Stursberg and Cocking, 1972 - 1986; F-31-2-1; 27 cm of textual records 20 sound recordings 1 moving image document; Physical description: sub-series includes 35 audio cassettes, 10 audio reels, and 6 3/4" videocassettes (Umatic tape).
    Subseries consists of materials used for the writing of Gordon Shrum: An Autobiography with Peter Stursberg, edited by Clive Cocking. This book was conceived by Darrel Zarn of the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies at SFU. He approached Peter Stursberg, an experienced journalist, who conducted a series of oral history interviews with Shrum in 1983. In order to fund the interviews, they were conducted under the oral history program of the Public Archives (now the National Archives) of Canada and the Parliamentary Library. Stursberg also made a 21/2 hour video interview of Shrum at the Instructional Media Centre at SFU. In addition, he interviewed nine of Shrum's friends and Shrum's son to provide material for the books's introduction. Because Stursberg was occupied with other projects, Clive Cocking a Vancouver writer and editor was hired to complete the project. Cocking conducted a series of supplementary interviews in 1985 to clarify statistics and other facts from the oral history interviews. Unfortunately, Shrum passed away suddenly before the manuscript was completed. The finished book appeared in 1986 through the support of SFU and the University of British Columbia.
    The subseries contains transcripts, background materials, notes, drafts, U-matic videos, audio reels, and audio cassettes.
    Stursberg, Peter; Cocking, Clive
    - Dr. Gordon M. Shrum: his recollections, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-1 (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2207, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2208, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2209, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2210, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2211, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2212)
      Moving images
      OBJ-2207, OBJ-2208, OBJ-2209, OBJ-2210, OBJ-2211 and OBJ-2212 are also available in .mov format.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item29, F-31-item30, F-31-item31, F-31-item32, F-31-item33, F-31-item34.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 1, January 31, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-2 (Audio reel OBJ-1036, Audio cassette OBJ-3042, Audio cassette OBJ-3043)
      Sound recordings
      Duration: 1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item19, F-31-item1, F-31-item2.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 2, February 2, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-3 (Audio reel OBJ-1038, Audio cassette OBJ-3044, Audio cassette OBJ-3045)
      Duration: 2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.3 (ref), F-31-item3, F-31-item4.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 3, February 7, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-4 (Audio reel OBJ-1037, Audio cassette OBJ-3046, Audio cassette OBJ-3047)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.5, C-31-2-1-1.6, F-31-item5, F-31-item6.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 4, February 9, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-5 (Audio reel OBJ-1035, Audio cassette OBJ-3048, Audio cassette OBJ-3049)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.7, C-31-2-1-1.8, F-31-item7, F-31-item8.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 5, February 14, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-6 (Audio reel OBJ-1034, Audio cassette OBJ-3050, Audio cassette OBJ-3051)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.9, C-31-2-1-1.10, F-31-item9, F-31-item10.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 6, February 16, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-7 (Audio reel OBJ-1033, Audio cassette OBJ-3052, Audio cassette OBJ-3053)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.11, C-31-2-1-1.12, F-31-item11, F-31-item12.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 7, February 21, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-8 (Audio reel OBJ-1032, Audio cassette OBJ-3054, Audio cassette OBJ-3055)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.13, C-31-2-1-1.14, F-31-item13, F-31-item14.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 8, February 23, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-9 (Audio reel OBJ-1031, Audio cassette OBJ-3056, Audio cassette OBJ-3057)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.15, C-31-2-1-1.16, F-31-item15, F-31-item16.
    - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Peter Stursberg, session 9, February 28, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-0-10 (Audio reel OBJ-1030, Audio reel OBJ-1029, Audio cassette OBJ-3058, Audio cassette OBJ-3059)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-1.17, C-31-2-1-1.18, F-31-item17, F-31-item18.
    - Interviews: Robert Williams, Arthur Erickson, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3060)
      Robert Williams; Erickson, Arthur; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-9.
    - Interviews: May Bennett, Anita Tozer, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3061)
      May Bennett; Tozer, Anita; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-10.
    - Interviews: Grace McCarthy, Gordon B. Shrum, Arthur Erickson, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3062)
      McCarthy, Grace; Shrum, Gordon; Erickson, Arthur; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-11.
    - Interview: George Volkoff, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-3063)
      Volkoff, George; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-12.
    - Interview: Patrick McTaggart-Cowan, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3064)
      McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-13.
    - Interviews: N.A. "Larry" MacKenzie, Robert Bonner, Hugh Keenleyside, Grace McCarthy, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3065)
      Larry MacKenzie; Bonner, Robert; Keenleyside, Hugh; McCarthy, Grace; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-14.
    - Supplementary inteview, Gordon Shrum interviewed by Clive Cocking, session 1, 6 April 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-3066, Audio cassette OBJ-3067)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-19.1, C-31-2-1-19.2.
    - Supplementary inteview, Gordon Shrum interviewed by Clive Cocking, session 2, 13 April 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-3067, Audio cassette OBJ-3068, Audio cassette OBJ-3069)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-19.3, C-31-2-1-19.4.
    - Supplementary inteview, Gordon Shrum interviewed by Clive Cocking, session 3, 4 May 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-3069, Audio cassette OBJ-3070, Audio cassette OBJ-3071)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-19.4, C-31-2-1-19.5, C-31-2-1-19.6.
    - Supplementary inteview, Gordon Shrum interviewed by Clive Cocking, session 4, 18 May 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-3071, Audio cassette OBJ-3072, Audio cassette OBJ-3073)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-19.7, C-31-2-1-19.8.
    - Supplementary inteview, Gordon Shrum interviewed by Clive Cocking, session 5, 25 May 1985; F-31-2-1-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3073, Audio cassette OBJ-3074, Audio cassette OBJ-3075, Audio cassette OBJ-3076)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-31-2-1-19.9, C-31-2-1-19.10, C-31-2-1-20.
    - Shrum, Gordon interview, unedited (*) 1/4, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 31-1)
    - Shrum, Gordon interview, unedited (*) 2/4, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 31-1)
    - Shrum, Gordon interview, unedited (*) 3/4, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 31-1)
    - Shrum, Gordon interview, unedited (*) 4/4, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 31-1)
    - Shrum, Gordon interview, edited bound (*), 1983; F-31-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Video interview notes, 1983; F-31-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Autobiography background materials, 1972 - 1985; F-31-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Autobiography introduction materials, 1985 - 1986; F-31-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Williams, Robert interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Bennett, May and Tozer, Anita interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - McCarthy, Grace interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Volkoff, George interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - McTaggart-Cowan, Pat interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Bonner, Robert interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - McKenzie, Norman interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Keenleyside, Hugh interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Shrum, Gordon B. interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Erickson, Arthur interview for introduction (*), 1985; F-31-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 31-2)
    - Shrum, Gordon supplementary interview (*) 1/2, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
    - Shrum, Gordon supplementary interview (*) 2/2, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
    - Autobiography draft, 1/2, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
    - Autobiography draft, 2/2, 1985; F-31-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
  - General biographical materials, 1973 - 1985; F-31-2-2; 1 cm of textual records 3 photographs
    The subseries consists of records about the life of Gordon Shrum and includes photographs, transcripts, and a scrapbook. The transcript is from an interview conducted in July 1973 by Allen Specht as part of an oral history project at the University of British Columbia. Although the transcript includes a brief biography of Shrum, the main topic is the Canadian Officers Training Corps.
    Specht, Alan
    - Shrum, Gordon interview, 1973; F-31-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
    - Photographs, [19--]; F-31-2-2-0-2
      Photographic materials
    - Gordon Shrum scrapbook, 1983; F-31-2-2-0-3
  - Reminiscences of Gordon Shrum, 1982; F-31-2-3; 4 sound recordings; Physical description: series consists of 4 audio cassettes (originals); no access copies have been made.
    Sub-series consists of interviews with various individuals relating their experiences with Gordon Shrum. Interviews were conduted by D. Zarn and C. Duppereault. Interviewees were Harry Evans (SFU Registrar), Rob Watt (Vancouver Centennial Museum and later first Chief Herald of Canada), Lorne Davies (Director, Recreational Services and Athletics), and Professor James Wilson (Department of Geography).
    The sound recordings were arranged by the Archives in the 1980s as part of Record Group 100 (Audio tapes) in series RG100/11/25 (Special events > Reminiscences of Gordon Shrum). RG100 was a collection of materials of various provenance that was established by the Archives based on physical format (audio tapes). It has been re-organized as F-231 (SFU sound recordings collection), but some materials have been moved to more appropriate fonds or collections. These recordings were moved to F-31 in August 2012.
    Zarn, D.; Duppereault, C.
    Access to the original sound recordings is restricted due to the fragility of the physical medium. No access copies have yet been made; consult the reference archivist for information about access.
    - Mr. Harry Evans, Registrar SFU, May 28, 1982; F-31-2-3-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-572)
      Evans, Harry M.; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: 100/11/025.
    - Robb Watt, Centennial Museum, May 28, 1982; F-31-2-3-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-573)
      Watt, Robb; Sound recordings
    - Lorne Davies, Director Athletics, May 28, 1982; F-31-2-3-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-574)
      Davies, Lorne W.; Sound recordings
    - Professor J. Wilson, SFU Geography, June 29, 1982; F-31-2-3-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-575)
      Wilson, James W.; Sound recordings
- Shrum and SFU interviews, 1973 - 1989; F-31-3; 7 cm of textual records 5 moving image documents 3 sound recordings; Physical description: series includes 8 audio reels, 5 audio cassettes, 7 3/4" videocassettes (Umatic tapes), 2 VHS videocassettes, and 1 optical disk.
  Series deals with the relationship between Gordon Shrum and Simon Fraser University. Interviews and supporting materials emphasize Shrum's work at SFU in contrast to biographical materials that describe Shrum's entire life. Series contains unedited and edited transcripts and audio recordings of an interview of Gordon Shrum conducted in 1974 by Liisa Fagerlund, a librarian and University Archivist. The interview was part of an SFU oral history program.
  Series also includes recordings of several television shows in which Shrum is interviewed. There are two appearances on the Vancouver show, one broadcast in 1977 and another in 1985 which includes a presentation by Iona Campagnolo of a Lifetime Achievement Award to Gordon Shrum. There are also two episodes of the Jack Webster show: the September 9, 1980 show, in which host Jack Webster interviewed Shrum and SFU President George Pedersen; and another from November 15, 1983 which commemorates the life of Gordon Shrum upon the establishment of the Shrum Science Chair at Simon Fraser University.
  Series also contains textual material, and audio and video recordings of the dinner held in honour of Shrum to establish the "Gordon M. Shrum Chair in Science" November 19, 1983.
  Textual records; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
  Access to the original moving images and sound recordings is restricted due to the fragility of the physical storage media. However, some digitized access copies area available for specific recordings. Consult the reference archivist for information about access.
  - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Liisa Fagerlund, session 1, January 30, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-0-1 (Audio reel OBJ-1042, Audio reel OBJ-1043, Audio reel OBJ-1039, Audio reel OBJ-1044, Audio cassette OBJ-1047, Audio cassette OBJ-1048)
    Fagerlund, Liisa; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
  - Gordon Shrum interviewed by Liisa Fagerlund, session 2, February 21, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-0-2 (Audio reel OBJ-1041, Audio reel OBJ-1040, Audio cassette OBJ-1049, Audio cassette OBJ-1050, Audio cassette OBJ-1051)
  - Vancouver television show (CKVU program on SFU), 1977; F-31-3-0-0-0-3; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2217)
    Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    OBJ-2217 also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item73, V-31-3-0-2.
    - OBJ-2217-dgt.mov
  - Webster television show, appearance, September 9, 1980; F-31-3-0-0-0-4; 2 videocassettes 2 .mov files (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2215, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2216)
    Tape consists of interviews and discussions with K. George Pedersen, President of Simon Fraser University since 1979 and Gordon Shrum, first Chancellor of Simon Fraser University (1964-1968) on the occasion of Simon Fraser University's 15th anniversary. Recorded from commercial broadcast by Instructional Media Services SFU.
    Webster, Jack; Pedersen, Knud George; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    OBJ-2215 and OBJ-2216 also available in .mkv format.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item73, V-31-3-0-1, V-31-3-0-1a.
    - OBJ-2215-dgt.mov
    - OBJ-2216-dgt.mov
  - Webster television show, appearance, November 15, 1983; F-31-3-0-0-0-5; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2213)
    Webster, Jack; Shrum, Gordon; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .mov file also available in .mp4 and .mkv formats.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item52, V-31-2-2.
  - Shrum dinner / Chair in science: audio-visual recording, November 19, 1983; F-31-3-0-0-0-6 (Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2218, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2219, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2220, Videocassette: 3/4&quot; umatic OBJ-2221)
    OBJ-2218 is damaged and does not play. OBJ-2219 and OBJ-2220 are damaged and were captured for sound only, no picture.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item65, F-31-item66, F-31-item67, F-31-item68, V-31-3-0-1, V-31-3-0-2, V-31-3-0-3, V-31-3-0-4.
    - OBJ-2221-dgt.mov
  - Shrum dinner / Chair in science: sound recording, November 19, 1983; F-31-3-0-0-0-7 (Audio reel OBJ-1046, Audio reel OBJ-1045)
  - Vancouver television show, appearance, 1985; F-31-3-0-0-0-8; 1 videocassette 1 optical disk 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2214, Optical disc: dvd OBJ-2733)
    Item is a videotaped recording of the 1985 Vancouver Awards, hosted by Laurier LaPierre and broadcast on CKVU. Gordon Shrum was the recipient of a Lifetime Achievement Award, presented by Iona Campagnolo. Other award recipients include Betty Fox, recipient of the Vancouver Woman Award, Steve Fonyo, recipient of the Sweney Award for Supreme Achievement, Rick Hansen, recipient of the Terry Fox Award for Chivalry and Courage, and the Killarney High School Jazz Band, recipient of the Sweney Award for Best High School Band in Vancouver.
    Campagnolo, Iona; Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .mov file also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-31-item53, V-31-2-3.
  - Shrum, Gordon interview - notes and correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-31-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
    Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized)
  - Shrum, Gordon interview - unedited (*) part 1, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
  - Shrum, Gordon interview - edited (*) part 1, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
  - Shrum, Gordon interview - unedited (*) part 2, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
  - Shrum, Gordon interview - edited (*) part 2, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
  - Shrum, Gordon interview - edited (*) part 2, 1974; F-31-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 31-3)
  - Shrum science chair, 1980 - 1989; F-31-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 31-3)